construction is a miss nation charlie's mystical philosophy coal and religions
建设是一个怀念国的查理的神秘哲学煤炭和宗教
tradition that emphasizes life in agreement with
强调生活与传统相一致的传统
the hall de may work and do with and is the dao de
大厅可能与之相关并与之相关
jing created by mysterious of recall pilsen
由神秘的回忆皮尔森创造的静
which contains profile with them and insights what the homo range networks at
其中包含与他们的个人资料，并洞悉同质范围网络的作用
the find how is a like grimes de and showed it can be difficult
找到像是一个肮脏的德，并表明这可能是困难的
to make sense out of the poetry parables and I die and the other forms of
从诗歌寓言中讲得通，我死了，还有其他形式的
right thing that do clears your scriptures or something
正确的事情确实可以清除您的经文或其他内容
nevertheless we can find a lot of value inn in this video i would like to this
尽管如此，我们还是可以在这部影片中找到很多有价值的旅馆
costs on the hours with them for inner peace
与他们在一起的时间花费，实现内心的平静
[Music]
[音乐]
the hope is a content or philosophy that had already been very angry studies
希望是已经非常生气的研究的内容或哲学
culture where all about the work hard play hard
努力工作的文化
beam pro-actively unlocking your for potential
积极主动地释放您的潜力
achieving social status is what you get off the ghost
获得社会地位是你摆脱鬼魂的原因
stretching marcel spies capacity 6,000 min that compliment is evil
扩展马塞尔间谍的能力6,000分钟，恭维是邪恶的
certain degree of consumer is necessary for survival
一定程度的消费者是生存所必需的
and the live ate the critters of civilization highlight what the dew clears
活着的人类吃掉了文明的小动物，这突显了露水清除的一切
let there be alternatives to leave my life's be this a lesson burdened some lesson
让别的选择离开我的生活，这是一堂课，给我上了一课
glamor to this all comes down to living morin then the language was already that
这一切的魅力都归结为生活莫林，那么语言已经是
encompassing and driving force behind the universe far
宇宙背后的力量和驱动力
for peace of with them that might bring is closer to the hall was dead and the
因为与他们的和平可能会带到离大厅更近的地方，死了，
orange tape loose and current culture likely to be over stress or even in order
橙色胶带松动，当前培养可能会过分压力甚至井然有序
to achieve goals of 10 times how to lie rush xxlerator achievements
达到目标的十倍如何撒急xxlerator成就
boskabouter nobilities and pushed to heart the problem of this
boskabouter贵族和推销这个问题
behavior is this good foundation to
行为是建立良好的基础
do what we wanted to which results in a very and stable position a quote box
做我们想做的事情，以使报价框的位置非常稳定
cough and don tip at home do not stand formula will save those who there
咳嗽，不要在家里给小费，不要站着配方去救那些在那里的人
don't get very for those who tried to outshine others
对于那些试图超越别人的人来说不是很好
them their own light box corner hold'em selfridges knows the know-how of those who
他们自己的灯箱角落Hold'em selfridges知道那些人的专有技术
angry or their accomplishments they manage the function that or then
生气或他们的成就，他们管理的功能，然后
and shot so is better than i don't rush and toe tess don't buy things that we
和射击相比，总比我不着急和脚趾苔丝不买我们买的东西要好
can't afford don't lie about your abilities and don't show of even of all
负担不起，不要撒谎，也不要表现出所有
the time because you we put there even an extreme level narbonne and stressful
的时间，因为你我们把那里甚至是极端的纳博讷和压力
position this doesn't mean that we should en co wood and compression
位置，这并不意味着我们应该进行压缩和压缩
frank's it is Christmas time how to do so in a way that is best sustainable and giving
坦率地说，现在是圣诞节，您如何以最可持续的方式做到这一点，并给予
figuring out patty's two led's is softness about it
弄清楚帕蒂的两个led是软的
a follow-up to not standing under tip at home
对不在家小费的后续行动
it could be very beneficial to realize that softness is so you could know about it
认识到柔软是非常有益的，因此您可以了解它
greatest of home first wrote some lead acid about this and
最伟大的家庭首先为此写了一些铅酸，
a quote by which is therefore or test and most
因此，报价或测试和大多数
fielding substance that nothing is better than other occurs in the
没有什么比其他更好的调遣物质发生了
hart en ridgid lucas nothing can compete with it en squad how i port an intro
哈特·里吉德·卢卡斯（Hart en ridgid lucas）没有什么可以与它竞争的。
d'es in many ways when look at how our escort gets old
当我们的伴游如何变老时，他们会以多种方式
mountains and drock summer planet how does he do that
山和钝的夏天星球他是怎么做到的
repeating so a real of softness over and over again will eventually overcome
一遍又一遍地重复如此柔软的现实，最终将克服
the heart influence and chips us mounting and table
心脏的影响和阻碍我们安装和桌子
die eventually add up into one day
最终死了一天
undertaking this is the power of disziplin which means
承担这就是disziplin的力量，这意味着
at who does the same thing over and over again to achieve something back and
谁会一遍又一遍地做同样的事情来取得回报，
great vector in this process is the virtue of passions as if form or
在这个过程中，伟大的载体是激情的美德，就像形式或
softness and which would simply be eksept de sloanes or a natural process
柔软，可以简单地看作是斯隆或自然过程
another factor is the willingness to let go to the universe
另一个因素是愿意放弃宇宙
ourselves we can see with plantings tree people
我们自己可以看到种植树木的人
simple weekend wild tree and to grab economy
简单的周末野生树和抢经济
what's it and the led nature does the rest being soft also means being flexible
这是什么，主导性质是否使其余部分变得柔软也意味着变得灵活
people there to heart and brutal channel adapt to use situations easily and off
那里的人尽心尽意地适应和适应使用情况
and shop you to external circumstances when flexible the water we can adapt
并在柔性水的情况下让您适应外部环境
to the circumstances when rap breaks or form mountain
在说唱破裂或形成山峰的情况下
lion earthquake de val polarizer put what's on the other hand you just find
狮子地震瓦尔偏振镜另一方面，您只发现了什么
another way to flow 3m rasheed useless class in the grange
在农庄中流通3m rasheed无用类的另一种方法
of history you build a used look the 3rd lumberjack didn't want to cut dead
的历史，您建立了一个二手的外观，第三个伐木工人不想砍死
tree be caused a two-day within waist of time and energy the trie was so cricket
这棵树在时间和精力的束缚之内造成了两天，所以tri是如此tri
and ugly that this problem couldn't keep up
丑陋的，这个问题无法跟上
decent parcel shelf old fat in vogue such a malan surfing that the
像样的包裹架上的旧脂肪正在流行，这种马兰冲浪
streetrace especially cut down because they were used for mankind so the useless
街头赛特别减少了，因为它们被人类使用了，所以毫无用处
people at the pubs tree became the reason for its survival but about people
酒吧树上的人们成为其生存的原因，但关于人们
thought that the sad formations and i made it special and began to worship et
以为那可悲的阵形和我使它变得特别，并开始崇拜等
maaike holy object ar society expects to be useful
maaike圣物ar社会期望是有用的
good morning plush the thunderstorm halogen diligence good looking at sierra
早上好毛绒雷暴卤素勤奋好看塞拉
being you class a thousand geddes and respect and is also chinese or vice
是你们一千名的人和尊敬的人，也是中国人或副人
living stories single living virtually including been used for for the community
生活故事，几乎是单身生活，包括用于社区
what the dew knew and kind belgian sdh go against the grain
露水知道些什么，以及比利时sdh的种类与谷物背道而驰
by saying that use business is really really very useful in the case of the trie
说使用业务真的非常有用
useless nes led to is preservation to the come to us will see that we now show
没用的nes导致保存到我们这里将会看到我们现在展示的
process many designables already finished and c formula of trouble if
处理许多已经完成的可设计项目，如果有问题，则计算c公式
you aren't very caring it shows harm about it
你不是很在意它显示出它的危害
in cities be happy picasso it has people often the first month
在城市里，毕加索会很开心，第一个月常常有人
that get explodes for death penalty leaf flea Allah she came on surfpad
因死刑叶跳蚤阿拉而爆炸，她来到了冲浪板上
striving for external function is the semi striving for analysis
争取外部功能是分析的半努力
12,000 buy happiness and it certainly a thousand by inner peace
12,000可以买到幸福，内心的和平一定可以买到一千
anne kon jerry bit too much and camber by positions and eve also anxiety about
安妮·康·杰里（Ann kon Jerry）太过分了
the eersel to reach a provider with the music of bells
用铃铛音乐与供应商联系
dream fragile ebb and flow and there motor stuffed with the flash of 5 based and
梦想着脆弱的潮起潮落，电机充斥着基于5的闪光，
with one of the richest flavor so other designers satisfied till they
具有最丰富的风味之一，因此其他设计师对此感到满意，直到他们
forget there proper business der beg you pronoms the conditioner disorder
忘了那里适当的生意，乞求您的护发素紊乱
cenk deeply and door self-sufficiency idea how simple individuals as consignments
深思熟虑，自给自足的想法是多么简单的个人作为货物
hyde was a heavy burden under the aircondition's box
海德在空调箱底下是个沉重的负担。
maybe pronoms of of bitter suffering and quote de douwes c en ik to or
也许是苦难的代名词，或者引述杜威斯之声或
grabbing towards external cents tightly hole-in-one two msn natural is not on
紧紧抓住外部美分，两个msn自然不亮
line plus the download pc with chrome society seems to be completly revolver living
line和带有chrome社团的下载PC似乎完全可以用作左轮手枪了
dress and perhaps this is one of the main reasons why so many people are poor en
着装，也许这就是为什么这么多人贫穷的主要原因之一
and tidy presence this dress and fully and rocks and each half wow a bit better
整洁的穿着这件衣服，充分地和岩石，每个一半都好一点
stop striving and let go and horny faint longer the grant of life will find out
停止努力，放手，让角质晕厥的生命更长久，就会发现
that many things will come to and that the thousand take much and a materialist
将会有很多事情发生，而上千种会花费很多，而一个唯物主义者
i sense to be satisfied when bird transforme pounds the oil
当鸟变油时，我感到很满足
a lot of sitting games was in
参加了很多坐姿比赛
then father to keep on living even animals and hibernation not
父亲甚至不让动物和冬眠继续生活
just enough to survive the codes and scarcity of winter
刚好可以度过冬季的准则和稀缺
5 following a more natural course we will most likely end up in places
5遵循自然路线，我们很可能最终会出现在某些地方
cash on delivery in equipment, there was a nature the act of striving to blinds
设备货到付款，自然而然地努力去做盲人的行为
the finish it already on the possibilities that life process and this
在生命过程和可能性的可能性上完成它
weekend simply take with old effort so it knows harmes to lay
周末只需花些力气，就可以知道躺着的危害
down the arms for a while and just experience what the universe house in
放下手臂一会儿，然后体验一下宇宙中所容纳的东西
store for as capable or opportunities 3 striving for conception future
为能力或机会而存储3为构想未来而奋斗
thank you for watching
谢谢你的收看
[Music]
[音乐]